all right ladies and gentlemen good
morning let's head to our office and let
me show you the starting balance for
this week on the account wrong
phone right phone so right now the
starting balance for this week is going
to be
$444,000 and obviously last week we had
the unnecessary loss because we moved
our stop loss and got greedy I don't
know why I'm laughing at this point we
blew the account boys the
44,000 so now let's get into the markets
for this week now bear with me I'm
usually bigger well I am usually
bigger but I'm used to a bigger setup
this a setup we're working with this
week no AC and no monitor so please bear
with me I'm going to try my best to show
you guys what I usually see on a big
screen so the first market for the week
is going to be Euro AUD so Euro AUD as
of right now on the daily time frame is
creating a beautiful absolutely
beautiful inverted Head and Shoulders
left head right shoulder perfect retest
from this level of supporting resistance
perfect retest from that daily EMA
perfect bullish engulfing everything
that I would want to see on this trade
4H hour time frame we are having the
reaction exactly how I would want to we
have support resistance resistance
resistance resistance resistance break
retest then we have the EMA when you go
down to the 1 hour we have a beautiful
beautiful 1H hour higher low higher high
pullback the only thing is I can't buy
right now right under this area of
interest only way I could buy is if we
were to be like this above it so if we
break and retest and give us that
engulfing I would enter the trade I did
not enter the trade here because as you
can see at the time below this is on
Friday of last week currently right now
you can see that this is now Monday
morning can never enter a trade on
Friday you can only enter a trade at the
beginning of the week never at the end
of it so as of right now we're waiting
for a quick little break and retest to
enter this trade to the upside Euro AUD
is my number one pair for the week next
we have USD CAD which I'm interested in
executing this position once and only we
have a break and retest under the
structure that I'm about to show you
right now you can very clearly see right
here on the weekly time frame that we
currently have a very strong rejection
from the EMA rejection from the level of
support support resistance and
resistance we have a lower low lower
high and rejecting all that from right
there when we go down to the 4-Hour time
frame you can very clearly see that the
4-Hour time frame is indeed accumulating
at this this area when you go to the 1
hour time frame you can see how it's
created this very strong level of
support and resistance here so basically
what I'm waiting for in order for me to
execute this position right here is
going to be a very quick break and
retest under this 1 hour time frame to
then enter this position to the downside
as right now it's doing the complete
opposite so all we simply have to do is
remain Patient next and technically last
pair that I'm interested for the week
this week we only have three markets
usually we have anywhere from 5 to 6 but
honestly the less the better because
it's a lot easier to keep up with them
and you don't have to constantly decide
oh do I want this one do I want the
other one no it's just one at a time so
this one is going to be probably the
next favorite one which is going to be
Euro GBP Euro GBP on the weekly time
frame we currently have a very strong
higher low we're lower low lower high
lower low higher high higher low very
clean bullish rejection Candlestick
daily time frame you can see how we are
indeed rejecting this level of
resistance resistance resistance support
support which is good I need that to
confirm that once we do break and retest
above that it's going to then do what it
did before break and retest and then
head to the upside as of right now it's
using it as resistance so we got to wait
for the break and retest above the 4H
hour time frame same exact thing you can
clearly see how it is a very strong
level of resistance all we're waiting
for for this Market is for it to have a
push retest and enter the trade to the
upside it's a very significant level of
support and resistance and this is
exactly what we need in order to enter
this position patients pays and then
what that I'm a little bit iffy about
I'm like whatever about it is GBP JPY
GBP JPY very clearly on the weekly time
frame we have a lower low all we're
waiting for is on the weekly time frame
for it to have a lower high retest that
structure level and then we can enter
this position to the downside so just
waiting for a retest to then sell but as
of right now my number one pair of me
interested in entering a position is
going to be Euro
Au so I'm extremely tired it is
currently right
now
11:38 in the morning and we're literally
about to hop on the jet G4 back to Miami
came out here to check out my tobacco
farm couldn't do any videos we're
keeping it as private as exclusive as we
possibly can and um it's quick 2-day
trip 50 60k a jet [__] it why not
somebody has to do it Jet's there if I
don't pay for it who is right [__] with
something so we're on our way back now
to Miami and we have Police Court
waiting for us so we can go back home
and avoid all the traffic that we're
about to catch when we get back home
this is this is what making money is
about it's about hacks like you think I
want to pay 50 60,000 for a jet and then
for when I land for me to go sit in
traffic for an hour [__] that I'll pay
an extra can't disclose how much and I
get a police escort from the airport to
the house if I'm paying for the jet to
save time but then I get off the Jet and
then I waste the time that I saved in
traffic I did nothing so what I'm going
to do do is I'm going to get the escort
so I can resave that time how do I
resave that time with money money is not
real but time is all right but actually
before we leave literally the pilots are
waiting for us on the jet it is
literally right now
11:42 and don't ask me how but we
brought this from the United States it
ended up in my bag I don't know how this
is my bag don't ask me but the people
that have been serving us here at the
house the ma and the Two Chefs they've
been absolutely phenomenal and I always
leave tip and I'm looking for tip and
I'm like I'm I'm literally going through
my wallet all I have is like a couple
hundred buck I'm like I feel like such a
[__] cuz I usually tip a good amount
and then I find this and I'm like oh
this is it it's not that much it's like
1,500 bucks but I'm going to give him
this in all the money cash that I have
so I don't know I just want to see the
reaction how they're going to
[Laughter]
reactos
for oh my God
funny like you can give somebody in the
United States $10,000 like cash like a
big stack like this and they'll be like
thanks like they they won't give a [__]
you give lot of people out here2 $3,000
and you like look at these people bro
they're like the most grateful people on
the face of the Earth like look at them
look at him look at them
look I don't believe it bro I'm telling
you Latin countries and other people
that appreciate things way more than
people in the US people in the US feel
like they're entitled to it that's why I
love coming back here and giving back
more than I possibly can so really
really great people
[Music]
all right so good thing trade is still
not giving us the break and reach that
we want to USD CAD still waiting for the
rejection break and retest under and
then Euro gvp still waiting for the
break and
retest so now en dra our
[Music]
[Applause]
flight you guys about to see how we're
about to catch no traffic right now on
the way home all right so right now it
is currently
4:07 it should take us about an hour and
a half to get home from this private
airport to the house let's see if this
life happens oh my God I'm just playing
with him now yeah I'm never on this side
of this I'm usually always like in the
front how to feel I feel like I'm
pulling him over now oh my
God L good evening ladies and gentlemen
it is currently 10:3 in the afternoon
afternoon afternoon look at that you
know how FR I am 1:03 in the morning so
if we did not take the private jet
earlier or the police has we would have
not been able to get half of the stuff
we wanted to get done to get it done
currently right now the account is at
44,000 still no trade in the accounts
because the market simply hasn't given
us an opportunity so let's see what the
market has done so Euro AUD we've been
anticipating for price to have a
breaking retest of this area to head to
the upside we have clearly not had that
break and retest to head to the upside
simply waiting for break retest to then
buy USD CAD same exact thing we are
waiting for price to break retest to
then sell daily time frame closed with a
daily dogee which is great CU confirming
that it's accumulating and rejecting at
this area here so we're simply waiting
for that to happen waiting for the break
and retest to then sell Euro AUD back at
it real quick the daily time frame
didn't close super bad it's decent I
anticipate for this next daily
Candlestick to have a daily bullish
engulfing and then the next day we'll
have a pullback then head to the upside
so this might be a trade for Wednesday
night lastly is going to be Euro gvp so
we did have a big red day but we are
pulling back up to this level of support
here which is clearly support and
resistance where we could have a
reaction from but not interested in
doing anything down here until we don't
break and retest above so basically
we're waiting for one break and retest
two break and retest and three break and
retest a little interested in GJ if it
does manage to make it all the way back
into this area we are kind of already on
our way there but I'm not going to be
interested until we don't actually pull
up to this level of support and
resistance so have to be very patient
and be on the lookout for this Market to
give us that opportunity once we are
there
so not much other else to do other than
instead of forget I'll see you guys in
the morning all right ladies and
gentlemen trade update it is currently 3
in the afteron afternoon so no action in
the accounts but we will have action
tonight tonight we will enter battle
once again tonight we're going to enter
battle and take these
$44,000 to $100,000 tonight and you know
what to go enter battle tonight I need a
new watch cuz I don't I don't know I
don't I got tired of my whole entire fet
of watches you know what let me go buy a
new watch today [__] it somebody's got
to do it right so we're going to go buy
watch for tonight's battle so this is
I'm going to show you guys how when you
raise your status and your mind and who
you want to become by let's say getting
a watch or a car how the money is going
to come right back we're going to test
this live today I'm going to go buy a
new Richard Mill right now and as I buy
it I'm going to make that money back
tonight because I've just opened my mind
to new things or I could be totally
wrong and I can buy the watch and lose
the money tonight and I [__] look
like an idiot but I highly doubt that's
going to happen so trade update right
now update on your VP we're having a
daily bullish engulfing Candlestick
exactly what we've needed this why I'm
saying we're going to have a battle
tonight because this Market is currently
having the break that we wanted now
we're going to wait for the retest in
order to enter this trade to the upside
obviously we can't enter a trade now
because it is not the right session to
trade GJ has pulled back to the area of
Interest exactly how I wanted to we had
the wick of the round psychological
level 18700 rejection from the 4our EMA
and then 1 hour price action is perfect
so it's our second battle we can
potentially enter tonight and then
lastly is going to be USD CAD where we
are currently having rejections from up
here and the daily time frame is having
a daily dogee Candlestick Euro AUD
currently we're waiting for the break
and then the retest for price then head
to the upside so USD CAD break and
retest Euro AUD break and retest this
one we're looking to enter very soon GJ
and then Euro GBP we're looking to enter
very soon
tonight we will be going to battle so
armor up with me we can beat the
market it's pretty good right it's a
pretty good uh no no super
cringe but before that we need a new
watch so let's go get the the rich meal
I bet that's not cringe [__] it
makes it less cringe okay
exactly that looks crazy I forgot you
have this watch yeah bro I love it
insane I wear this watch more than like
anything honestly cuz it's like subtle
and lowkey you know no not really like
should I should I polish it's not subtle
to me but it looks insane on your no
this not subtle the white goat is insane
it pops so much bro I don't know why try
this yeah let me see I'm not a big these
are inexpensive bro inexpensive
inexpensive I don't say cheap what I say
inexpensive cuz nothing here is cheap
right no you're right nothing all right
let's see what you
got let's see let's see what's in the
magical box cuz even I don't know bro
changes every day let's see how does
that even work well I have 20 people
here just sell Richards before I get to
work bro that white one bro Alex it's
actually crazy like anyone sees that on
your wrist they'll it'll blow their mind
so it's 380,000 380 yeah yeah this
thing's stup sexy the gold on the sides
it pops so much with the white bro cuz
there's a black version of this one too
yeah but that looks nothing like this
yeah no and it's like small but big at
the same time mhm and then did oh you
have two of these yeah that's what I I
can give you a very nice like brother
deal on that what's the brother deal
inexpensive thank you it's very
inexpensive know my dad always corrects
me he says never say your product is
cheap call it inexpensive which is true
right it's a very good word yeah it's
way better very good word well what do
you just call it it's at a good price
it's at a good price yeah so what you
just picked up it's limited to 50 pieces
in the world it's the Asia Edition it's
carbon super light I think it's cool
like it's good contrast from your like
your white watch your gold watch you
know what makes this like the Asia
Edition the the color way oh like the
black and gold black bro I like this one
I think I'm going take this one that's
it easy to sell to this guy
bro I mean bro I'm not a window shop all
right trade update after just getting
scammed your gvp still waiting for the
rejection USD CAD still waiting for the
break and re this under Euro AUD still
waiting for the break and reach this
above so right now no traits I got to go
to Steve now should I get Steve should I
get Steve something you didn't know
anything that he wants like got him he
didn't like Rings oh he wanted a rope
chain I could get that for like 2K a
crazy rope chain to blow his mind how
fast and you very quick like 20 30
minutes yeah like 20 you can sit here we
can order some food quick how big it'll
look big are you yeah or put on speaker
yeah yeah I'm here I'm here what's up
Stevie Neil can I have a was it a Sprite
or you want a spr yeah just give it to
Alex please all right bet yeah I'm going
to give away okay all right bet so
should I give him this chain in the
middle of him giving away a watch yeah
I'm going feel like such a [__] giving
away a chain he's giving away R right as
soon as he finishes be like bro you're
always doing this dog and I was just
with Neil and I just had 5K extra and I
just bought you this cuz he said you
loved it he'll love it okay the biggest
one it's going to the biggest one yeah
you think he'll like this yeah is it the
same length though 22 yeah it just looks
shorter because yeah it looks shorter
you look like some kind of mafia boss so
like days like today is where it makes
me want to live down here bro I'm like
[__] I should be a city
boy but then I realized I'm like do I
really want to go downstairs and walk
into this right here it's
construction probably not God Steve are
you [__] kidding
me oh my God and then I I got sent out
in a wheelchair and Selena saved me a
s got another
one oh my that's a gambling
one thank you so much Che thank you bro
thank
you you saved
me oh my gosh this is so beautiful yeah
you was telling me you like this
no did you always give him back you know
what yeah what going on
right the [__] going
On's a back
day oh what's
[Music]
up is this a real
belt yeah oh [__] that's Sugar's belt
this is Sugar's belt oh [__] it is yeah
he gave it to me he gave you this belt
yeah this was sugar one oh [__] that I
was I was the first guy to believe in
him like like hardcore bro I was telling
him he was world champion and [__]
before anybody gave a [__] about sugar I
don't know why I just had a feeling I
feel like a champ with the S right now
all right so Steve just gave us two
board yo shout out to Steve thank you
Steve welcome giving us two board
appreciate you thank you very much all
right see you give and then you get give
him a chain and then they get two boards
[Music]
all right trade up there boys so we just
got back home right now from Steve's
house and we have an unexpected
guest my cousin my cousin Oh Come On
Son Come On Son all right all right all
right so as you guys can see I got my
Richard mail and he just took it from me
but it's okay cuz we're about to put him
on to trading and you're going to tell
me what trade I'm going to take right
now all right how old are you 15
15 get him all right so I'm so I'm 6'4
all right I don't know how tall are you
63 no no no if I'm 6'4 you can't be
taller than me so I'm 6'4 you have to be
like 69ine all right does that make
sense all right all right take a seat
come on come here sit down all right so
we're going to do a trade update so he's
been trading he's been following the
series for how long we've been following
the whole trading stuff six months six
months have you made any money trading
or no a little bit how much is a little
bit I like 1,000 1,000 yeah okay so
we're about to risk tonight
$444,000 so trade update what time is it
right here on this phone what time does
it say 9:06 p.m. 9:06 so it's 9:06 how
much money do we have in the trading
account right now
44,6 to and 7 what's the most amount of
money you've risk in one
trade like 1,000 okay so we're about to
risk 44,000 on this trade [__] up it's
your ass
all right all right okay so first one is
the Euro GBP so eurogbp we've been
waiting all day for it to have the break
have the retest and as of right now
we're about to be interested in
executing this position we're having the
retest exactly how I wanted it to when
you go down to the 1 hour it's having
the bullish engulfing exactly how I
wanted to and when you go down to the 30
minute it's having well the 15 minute
it's having the shift of structure
exactly how I wanted
to what would you do would you take this
trade right now or not no why why I
don't like it why don't you like it tell
me tell me
why oh no this is not going to be good
all right let's go to another market
right so if we don't like one market we
can go to a different one GJ right GJ we
had the retest exactly how I wanted it
to this area of Interest daily time
frame did close a little strong to that
area I don't like that and it closed
above
18700 let me just put this at the round
psychological level
8700 and when you go down to the 4 Hour
the 4 Hour went very much bullish and
we're above the EMA and we're above the
structure level not good right do you
like this one or no no why not the EMA
is 29 oh the EMA okay all right all
right then we have Euro AUD which we're
waiting for this break and retest never
happen then we have USD CAD which we're
waiting for this break and retest hasn't
happened all
right this is the one
this is the one all right yeah this the
one all right so you're going to take
the trade right
now
sweating all right ready all right
go I want to do it bro why just just
risk 100% it's not a big deal risk 100%
is insane you know you're going to risk
the whole 44,000 so so if if the trade
loses I don't cuz I know you give me the
money back so I don't really give a
[__] I'm kidding all right so this trade
we might execute it very very soon we
might execute it within the next 30
minutes to 45 minutes um because what I
want to wait for is a little bit more
price action I want to see how this
trade reacts once it retests this level
like this trade is literally about to
take off like if this Candlestick goes
right back above this one I'm going to
probably execute this trade immediately
it's actually a very small stop loss
like I'll probably even make the stop
loss longer I make it 15 Pips because it
is a very very small stop loss and I see
very very very great upside potential on
this market so I I can see this trade
going from here easily all the way up to
this point right here for a 1 to three
risk to reward um I don't see any
friction on The Daily time frame other
than like this structure point right
here but even if price where to then
stop at that point that's still a 1 to2
it's currently Tuesday night so we still
have Tuesday nights Wednesday morning
Wednesday night Thursday morning and
Thursday night so we still have like a
solid four more sessions left which I
think there's enough momentum to get to
that point right there and I don't see
any friction on the 4our for this trade
unless it's somewhere around here but
then at that point we'll already re be
up a solid amount so yeah we'll update
back in like the next like 15 20 minutes
I just want to see if price can break
like if price can just break above this
area again here just even start wicking
above it yeah that's going to be my
indication that this is a higher low and
then it's going to start creating a
higher high to head to the upside right
it all right thanks for nothing all
right ladies and gentlemen trade update
is currently 2:30 in the morning and no
trade has been taken we actually avoided
this loss or Draw that right now but let
me show you let me show you my cousin
bro this guy this guy can't hang dud
look at this guy that's how he wants to
be a profitable
Trader this
generation this the perfect example of
patience pace so we avoided this massive
30 minute draw down or 1 hour
Candlestick I was ready to execute this
position literally as soon as this
Candlestick closes that morning star
formation but I always wait my 15 to 30
seconds to execute the position and
would you look at that price decided to
have a push to the downside so avoided
this loss perfectly and this just Pro
you once again it is 2:32 in the morning
so this is why I like trading London
session because volume kicks in
obviously this volume just happened to
kick in the wrong way this should have
happened to the upside which should have
been beautiful so no I'm not looking to
enter this trade right now because oh
Alex but you're going to get a better
entry it's like no dude that's not how
this works bro like the trade if it was
my it meets my strategy it's supposed to
go up from here not down from here this
does not mean I get a better entry so
right now I'm not fully interested in it
and until we don't get a better
rejection to the upside then we have GBP
JPY where we are currently waiting for
this price to have a clean pull back
into here and then have our rejection to
the downside which we currently are
having that pullback so I and then wait
for an engulfing around this area to
potentially enter this Market I'm going
to be on the lookout for this one even
though it doesn't look the cleanest Euro
AUD no break and retest above and USD
CAD still waiting for the break and
retest on there so for right now no
trades cousin knocked out 2:30 in the
morning and I'll probably be oh
[__] all right ladies and gentlemen good
morning look who decided to finally wake
up good morning guys so currently right
now it
is 12: in the morning or afternoon yeah
in the afternoon still no trade update
so as you guys can see the account is
still at
$44,000 and the trade from last night if
we would have actually executed it we
would have taken a massive loss you
wouldn't know cuz you fell asleep yes
sir why' you fall asleep a lot of work
this guy can't hang this generation
can't hang look at this guy all right
bro bro you keep falling for bro bro all
right so right here basically we were
waiting for a retest to then head to the
upside that did not happen so we simply
did not execute this trade now we are
having a reaction from this level of
support because it is a very strong
respected level of support support
support resistance support and support
so we might buy here very soon as crazy
as it seems even though the 4H hour time
time frame is bearish I'm just going to
be on the lookout for some potential
entries on this trade I'm going to be
waiting for something like a little
break and retest to then buy this trade
to the upside and it's still in my
interest GJ yesterday we avoided a loss
so on this pullback right here we never
got our engulfing Candlestick to the ENT
of the trade to the downside so we
avoided this loss to Perfection price
simply continued heading to the upside
basically we were waiting for the
pullback here to then sell then did not
have that pullback did not have the
rejection we wanted to avoid this loss
I'm still interested in the sells just
not yet like I think this daily time
frame has to close like that then the
next day could be the push as you guys
can tell it's Wednesday we basically
have the rest of tonight tomorrow
morning so we basically have three more
sessions left in this week for the
market to like give us opportunities to
make money so GJ might be one of those
markets that can potentially make us
money then we have Euro AUD which we're
still waiting for this break and retest
above which looking at it on the daily
if the daily time frame closes like this
I'll probably enter the position down
here which would still be an ideal buy
even though the 4our time frame is
bearish I'll probably wait for a little
bit a body close Above This lower high
structure point so I can take it
straight to the upside so a little break
and retest above that to then enter that
buy or we have USD CAD which we might
just enter the sell at a rejection from
up here and not wait for that break and
retest we got to we got to see all the
trades right now are still lining up
there's still plenty of opportunities we
just have to be very patient I like this
one right here USD Cad and I like Euro
AUD for breaking R this buys GJ F and
then Euro GBP F so we'll check back in
in about an hour or two hey what's going
on brother my bad I know I'm blowing you
up no it's okay no bad news is what they
said the two to three weeks out so look
I'm I'm cumin brother right like we we
find a solution to [__] everything
yeah could we just get it done [__] man
what a [__] mission stupid Bugatti
bro just pisses me off cuz I want to
[__] drive my car dude pay 50k a
month for it and I can't cuz it's stupid
belt dude like and it's annoying because
Bugatti [__] you don't
assuming [__] man it's just a belt why
do we have to go to Bugatti and do
everything at Bugatti and wait 3 weeks
for the parts that come from
Paris we'll figure it out watch I'll put
I'll put my [__] Gucci belt on that
[__] bro get out of here trade update
man I'm pissed off now USD CAD we have
had a ginormous Wick happen towards the
last hours of the day very very
interesting daily time frame has closed
with a humongous daily doe Candlestick
this will fill today it's going to fill
this Candlestick tonight we have
Wednesday London session as a battle
coming very soon then we have Thursday
New York and Thursday London this is
loading we're going to be entering this
trade very very soon next we have Euro
GBP which we avoided this loss last
night we might be entering new positions
at this point here but I don't want to
buy against this ginormous daily bearish
engulfing candas they clearly were in a
consolidation I was going to buy once we
broke and retested out of this
consolidation to the upside and then on
GBP JPY we were going to be interested
in taking a sell once we had a break and
retest of this trade to then head to the
downside so we're still waiting for this
break and retest to then sell and then
we are still waiting for this trade
right here to have the breaking reaches
above this one probably won't happen
anytime soon because we've had the
strong daily dogee so well actually you
know what I actually like Euro AUD a lot
because this daily dogee still makes
this daily structure move bullish this
is the higher low this is the higher
high and basically all I want is a
little quick break and retest above that
EMA and this level of support to enter
this trade to the upside I would love
for the 4 Hour to go bullish when I
enter this trade so we have to break
Above This lower high for price to then
continue heading to the upside so we are
technically right now in this bearish
cycle 1 hour channel on the 1 hour you
guys know I hate these channels not a
big fan of them I just want a little
quick break and read this out of this to
then head to the upside so you know what
I'm going to actually put this one as my
number one and then I'm going to put USD
CAD as my number two so right now we
have Euro AUD as my number one break and
retest for buys then we have USD CAD for
my number two we're waiting for breaking
retest for sales which I don't even know
if we'll wait for the retest of it like
we might just enter o no this is a
little bit tricky can't even lie yeah
we're just going to keep our eye on it
I'm very interested in entering this
very very soon and then Euro GBP not
interested GBP JPY I have it so I'm
moving it out for my fourth pair to now
my third pair of the order of the
markets that I'm actively interested in
so breaking retest to then sell and then
we have nzd CAD not looking and GBP CAD
not looking all right SI so it's been a
boring day been here all day probably
going to take a nap maybe hit the gym we
know we got to get fit and then see
where the day takes us stay tuned all
right ladies and gentlemen trade update
is
11:35 at night you can see right now
still no trades and history still
basically
nothing I'm getting ready for battle
tonight so we have literally tonight
London session tomorrow New York session
and then Thursday night London session
we got three 8 hour sessions left in
order for us to turn these $44,000 into
$100,000 so I'm about to do some
degenerate [__] I got to do it I got to
do it I'm going to break my trading plan
sadly I'm going to make money gladly and
then I got to drive the beetle back to
sadly but then I hit the go for the week
gladly you see is the math mathing you
get it makes sense makees sense okay
trade update so right now Euro AUD
currently we were waiting for a break
and retest above here to take the trade
to the upside no break and retest no
trade perfect loss avoided by simply
remaining patient so this is the exact
trade that I was waiting for and it
didn't happen USD CAD we're looking to
enter this trade this is why we got to
be patient earli we were interested in
potentially taking it but we're waiting
for the break and retest still very much
interested in it especially after this
ginormous liquidity pool Wick out
whatever you want to call it this is the
perfect type of trade that I'm looking
to enter tonight if that has a shift of
structure under this level right here
that closes under that in the next 20 2
minutes as you can see right here I will
then be interested in executing this
position right around here so I'm very
much interested in this very position
next GBP
JPY um had the exact same push to the
upside so we were anticipating for price
to reject here but we had a crazy run to
the upside to now retest this higher
level of structure I still believe that
we could continue heading to the
downside I just think it's going to take
a little bit more time so being very
patient on it Euro GBP keeping my eye on
it because we might enter on the break
and retest of this so right now if I
were to base it all off of the top
priority it would definitely be USD CAD
number one Euro GBP p number two and GBP
JPY number three so you guys are seeing
how throughout the week like it changes
like my number one pair for the week is
not my number one pair on Tuesday or
Wednesday that's why I picked top four
top five the markets that I'm going to
be interested in trading for the week
and then from there as the week goes as
the market starts unfolding I modify
base whatever is going to give me the
highest probability trade setup so for
right now 11:38 in the
evening no trades right now I'm going to
go take a shower and get ready for
battle tonight because we're we're doing
it we're going to do it tonight yep
morning ladies and gentlemen um it was a
brutal night last night in and out of
sleep all night and um yeah this morning
we thought we were on to something by
adding another position and we weren't
so as of right now we are currently in a
position that we are going to continue
to S and
forget I mean I literally just called it
last night it's not my first time
calling it all right boys so market
update we are currently up
41,000 so we're back at we're not even
back where we were last week and we just
did the dumbest thing ever we just
executed a loss right here because we
decided to enter this position right
around this area thinking that I was
just going to continue to go down like
when you don't sleep all night you just
start seeing [__] but then I go down to
the 1 hour I'm like but wait this price
definitely has the opportunity to come
back and retest this level of support
and resistance just how it did here it
could even go up further it could
literally go back up all the way up to
this area right around here before
actually going
down so the 80 lot that I took at that
point right there I simply closed it cuz
it was actually [__] so now I
currently in this position um it's
literally what I said yesterday we're
ready to execute it we're just waiting
for the right confirmations we just got
the break of the structure how I wanted
to enter the
EMA and yeah we're in this position now
so I'm just going to anticipate for
price to continue having a push to the
downside after this retest uh we avoided
a loss yesterday on Euro GBP avoided a
loss on GBP JPY and avoided a loss on
Euro AUD so we've been dodging bullets
all week finally managed to catch one
that aligns with the strategy so as of
right now I am probably going to take a
nap for an hour and I will keep you guys
updated
so this is currently 800 in the morning
trade
update and let's see where it is I think
New York session should come in and help
it out uh you know I'm going to actually
put an
alarm so yeah I'm going to actually put
an alarm right around on top of this
area of interest and the EMA and that
alarm I'm going to label it
as going to come
here edit and I'm going to label it
adds not
good and then we just save it and now we
set and forgot all right market update
not good this is so annoying [__] man
because like lose sleep for nothing and
it's so pointless
bro look at this like what I'm about to
show you right now is going to literally
show you New York session and leond
session having the exact same [__]
move [__] all right so you guys can see
here we are currently down 42,000 I mean
never mind we're back at $42,000 on the
balance of the account trade pulled back
higher than I expected you guys can see
here how literally London session is the
same as New York session this move with
this move this move with this move this
one with this one and these two are
[__] exactly the same so London New
York this is crazy dude
so annoying but I just hate I mean it
felt the Wake exactly how I said it was
going to do it but I just hated using to
sleep man because I could have just gone
to sleep normal and just woken up right
now at 9:48 in the morning and entered
the trade and then we're good I got a
full night's Worth to sleep not
emotionally drained not physically
nothing or whatever we're going to be
watching this trade so we're going to
continue to set and forget for now might
close soon might not can't continue to
lose using on this account so I'll
update you guys exactly what we're going
to do I don't see any other
opportunities in the market that I'm
interested in just yet EUR gvp nothing
gvp JPY nothing and Euro Au nothing we
update you guys on what we do right now
we're down about
$4,000 and uh yeah stay tuned I might
just take a nap and not even make a
emotional decision on this and just wait
for the technicals to do its thing we'll
update you guys all right guys trade
update I feel like I just did an
impulsive
decision not happy about it let me just
show you guys so basically we just
closed out the positions at break even
right about another $2,000
loss so trade was pulling back into this
area here I did not like the price
action on the 15minute and
um I literally closed on the top of that
wig being created I said [__] that I'm
going to get out of here I don't want to
be part of it cuz I think because this
bullish Eng golfing it's going to go
up but I let a 15minute bullish
engulfing Candlestick dictate that it is
stronger than this area of interest that
is stronger than this level of support
that's not going to be used as
resistance I let that be stronger than
the
trend whatever bro I'm like tired I want
to get some rest I'm going to probably
be entering the position soon till we
get a nice little engulfing I'm going to
definitely risk a lot more and we're
going to get a much bigger trade so stay
tuned for that decided to cover my end I
didn't want to blow it on this position
here because uh I don't know man just
lack of sleep lack of everything you
start seeing stuff so for now the
account is currently sitting at
41,000 all right boys today is a primal
example of a primal human being when you
get up every single day and you go to
battle you fight you fight fight and
fight and fight now you might get
knocked down but you get back up and as
soon as you get up you get knocked down
again but you continue to fight and
today is one of those examples where I
got knocked down oh I got knocked out
bad but I kept fighting trade updates
currently up
$62,000 we fight we continue continue to
fight and never stop we closed the
position at the top of this Wick up here
and literally we probably did the best
decision we could have done we closed
these two positions at a $2,000 loss for
a total
of60 Lots then we waited for price to
have its rejection now some of you guys
would have been like wow you closed for
no reason you could have still been
holding the trade you know what you're
right you're right dude but you wouldn't
be up $63,000 if I did not do that why
because I waited for this next entry
bearish engulfing confirmation uh
Evening Star formation under the EMA
rejection from the structure and I said
you know what okay fine you want to take
me out of break even and you want to
make me lose an extra 15 Pips from the
original entry that I originally had up
here from this to this point okay fine
I'll make it back by risking 170 more
Lots on this position before we had 160
Lots which was these positions right
here 880 + 80 is 160 you add all these
up and we have 330 so we essentially
almost doubled a little bit over the
risk that we had before but we got an
extra confirmation that we did not get
here and you know what I [__] with it
because yeah we lose 15 pits from the
entry but we gain 170 Lots it sucks on
the short term but on the long term
trust me it's going to pay
off man dude how stressful dude these
last couple of hours basically we
entered this trade as soon as it
engulfed right after this 30 minute
engulfing confirmation we literally got
stopped out at break even because of I
don't even I don't I don't even I don't
even know what to say dude I love this
4our Candlestick that just closed
literally 30 minutes ago I love how the
2hour time frame closed as well with
this 2hour bearish and engulfing
Candlestick what I'm going to be doing
now is I'm going to basically hide this
trade cuz technically it didn't even
happen and we're going to only focus on
this one beautiful 1 hour continuation
beautiful 30 minute look guys all we
need for this to be a big time home run
is going to be a body Candlestick
closure under this right here if the 30
minute closes under this structure point
right there if the 1 hour closes under
that structure point right there if the
2 hour closes under that structure point
and the 4H hour closes under that
structure Point boys we are golden
that's all I got to say so for now it's
1:31 in the afternoon we're about
$65,000 and we're going to continue to
hold this position not interested in any
other Market that is not USD CAD right
now Euro GBP I'm good GBP JPY I'm good
Euro AUD I am good
usdcad oh no dude
come on I dare you I dare
you I dare you that's all I got to say
good morning ladies and gentlemen well
it's supposed to be good evening or good
night ladies and gentlemen but it is
currently 2:06 in the morning this has
turned into my new morning this is where
I basically wake up and start my day
because I am clearly not going to sleep
at anytime soon because this challenge
as you guys can see in these last two
days have just been trade updates the
whole entire time usually we go take you
along with me wherever we go either to
the gym to the bank um to go do whatever
yeah we haven't really been doing
anything these last two days simply
because we have just been doing trade
updates my sleep schedule is bucked why
because we are not blowing this
challenge we are going to turn these
$40,000 into $100,000 now you may ask
yourself but Alex you were up 111
already why don't you close it the
takeprofit for the week because we're
not [__] we continue to set and
forget the trade and this trade has a
potential to be a quarter million doll
trade right now we are up
$50,000 with a balance of
$91,000 as you guys can see same exact
account trade history everything the
same this trade has the potential to be
A4 million so let me show you guys right
here so earlier we were obviously
ipating for price to have a body
Candlestick closure under this level and
if we did we were golden but price is
having it pull back to now retest this
level of support support support and
then resistance through here to head to
the downside so fair game not mad at it
but literally the moment we body
Candlestick close under this structure
level we're good we are home run but a
big but
if this movement happens to the upside
and we body Candlestick close above this
structure
point we're [__] we are Mega [__] so
right now we are literally in the middle
of that decision making are we [__] or
are we golden I think we're golden this
price is under this level right here it
just simply has more logic of it heading
to the downside than heading to the
upside so for now we're going to set and
forget next is going to be Euro gvp
which we were interested in taking this
position earlier but obviously no trade
setup presented itself so we simply did
not take the trade GBP JPY we were
interested in taking this trade setup as
well no trade setup has presented itself
and then Euro GBP we were waiting for a
break and retest above this area to take
this trade no breaking retest no trade
our only focus right now is on you USD
Cad and truthfully I can honestly hide
this ristor reward tool to over here
because we technically did not enter
that trade we're only involved in this
one so I have my take profit set at this
structure level right here on the 4our
which honestly it's a bit of a stretch
it's a nice 1 to three I don't really
have to do all that I can you know go
for a solid one to2 on this trade which
would be right around this level and
then on the 1 hour it would be right at
this level of structure right around
here more or less so we'll we'll shoot
for the one to two and then when price
gets there we'll determine to see what
we're going to do so as of right now
good morning ladies and gentlemen 2:09
in the morning and uh I'm probably going
to continue to be here for a bit longer
I'm going to try and maybe catch some
sleep if I see some good momentum cuz I
need to get back on my regular sleep
schedule it's literally all over the
place so for now set up no sleep
this I just I'm not going to say
anything I can't I'm not going to say
anything all I'm going to all I'm going
to do is just show you
guys I'm going to say things later right
right now I'm just going
to not say anything I'm going to say
things later cuz every single time I
talk the market hears me and when the
market it hears me it doesn't do what I
wanted to
do not going to say a word CU as soon as
I started talking it trade
update I am not going to say a
word all I'm going to going to say all
I'm going to
say that's exactly what the [__] I just
said how does this even happen I told
you guys the market hears me it hears me
no doubt in my mind how do you go from
being up
$120,000 to now this where the market
has had a 90% pullback from the last
move that it has just done the 4-Hour
time frame has had one of the craziest
bearish engulfing candlesticks rejection
EMA rejecting support and resistance how
in the [__] do we pull back 90% of that
and
literally 30 minutes how please Somebody
explain I told you the market is
listening to me it's listening to me so
now I can't I'm just not going to say a
word from this next sentence forward so
then this can do this I'll check back
in but look at this how are you going to
dude how in never in a million years
after a beautiful bearish engulfing
Candlestick rejection from EMA structure
look at this ginormous daily bearish
engulfing Camp look at look at the size
of that [__]
how do we retrace 60% of that bro I
don't know what to do I think as soon as
this goes back to break you and I'm just
going to fck is that that's see that's
me making an emotional decision I got to
make a technic I got to make a decision
based off of technical look at that
bullish engulfing Maru Candlestick bro
how in the [__] does that even work
I'm not being emotional I'm just
stressed I'm literally just stressed cuz
I've been looking at this [__] for two
and a half whole days why are you
looking at it Alex so don't
forget cuz I've been doing this for 11
weeks I want to finish this [__]
already there it is come on come on
break even come on come on
no no yes yes that's what I was waiting
for Break Even yes come on come
on come on come on no no
no no no stop
it stop
it no you have 5 Seconds to go back to
Rickie 5 4 3 2 2 one I'm actually
stressing right now that's the [__] up
part come on come
on come on come on [__] come on
go to [__] break even you
[__] it has to go down
bro
oh come here buddy huh huh think I
[__] forgot about you no no no no no
no no no I hav't no but I'm not done
with you y yet I'll be
back
oh yes yes yes in profit like we weren't
just up 70,000 [__] dollars this
shit's making me go crazy all right we
just got out right now uh
[__] I don't know dude I don't even
know how much that is um like $66,000 in
profit 5,000
whatever bro what a swing dude how do
you go from like 13 how do you go from
$70,000 in profit to then $113,000 in
drw down to now only making 4 grand tell
me how that
works couple weeks ago for Grand was a
lot yeah it was I mean clearly it is now
too we were begging for [__] $1,000
in profit yeah dude we're done for the
week There's no way I'm adding a
position right now on a Friday and it
just pisses me off because I know that
this shit's going to go down I just know
it so right now balance is at 45,000
show them the history cuz they always
want to see the [__]
history I literally feel like I just
took a weight off my shoulder
shoulders I got to I got to I got to
stop being so emotional bro I just got
to stick to the plan dude sad and
forget but [__] that I can't let you
guys down I can't let you
guys like I'm doing this so you guys
kind of don't have to like I'm showing
you guys the struggle and the the
reality of it so when you guys try to do
this yourselves if you decide to there
is there's hope there is somebody to to
resignate from going through whatever
you can potentially I'm going through
anything you can possibly go through in
this challenge fast wins fast losses
quick profit back to draw down Break
Even M trades Wick outs everything so
when you guys decide to do this you can
use me as an example and um hope you
guys to be your
joury what you come out of
bro I [__] knew it
man ah
bro that's why you got to trust your
instincts [__]
man bro I'm telling you it's going to go
down it just [__] has
to who's
it she lives the [__] good life she
doesn't even know what's going on look
at him
you know what's so you know what annoys
me that when I [__] this right usually
what I do to get my mind off of this is
to go out on my
boat but I don't have a boat right now
it's
broken it doesn't get any [__] worse
my boat almost sunk on me two weeks ago
pop up the clip literally sunk on me in
the middle of the river where there full
of [__] sharks
[__]
man ah dude what do I do I I I buy
another boat I don't have money to buy
another
boat whatever what you know what I think
I should just get out of
here so pretty much to wrap up the week
you know it's uh good to have the market
closed because now I can reflect on what
happened
and truthfully I got emotional but I
didn't get emotional about the money
it's just more of like the time like
it's the same I'm realizing it's a
pattern that's happening to me like at
the beginning I'm very strict even if I
lose I don't care and when I win I don't
care but that's like at the beginning
when I'm like two three weeks in four
weeks 5 weeks like we're literally on
week 11 right now so I'm like tired of
this you know I'm just like in the whole
routine and not sleeping same thing that
the last time and I realized that when I
get to this level is where I start
making mistakes I start [__] up
because I simply am human you know and
the difference between this time and
last time is that I accept that last
time I thought it was invincible and I
didn't think that that would affect my
trading at all but then obviously I blew
the account morning guys so we're
officially blowing the account and due
to that we're now here again but now I
know that and I accept that so this time
around since I know and I accept that I
know how to change that up so it happen
to me I could actually pass a challenge
which it's key for you guys out there
that are somewhat successful but want to
get to the next point is realizing what
you're doing wrong accepting it and then
actually taking action and executing and
implementing what you did wrong to then
fix it and start doing it right so if
I'm tired if I'm breaking my training
plan if I'm not setting and forgetting I
have to accept that and then adjust and
execute on doing it correctly for this
upcoming week so I accept it I accept
I've been emotional I accept that I have
not been sticking to my training plan
plan and I accept that I have not been
getting any rest so what do I do this
next week I simply do all of those
things and you're going to see the
difference from my results from this
week that's happening right now to next
week it's going to literally be night
and day difference and uh all I can say
is simply hit the Subscribe button make
sure you follow the account and if
you're new to the channel and new to the
challenge go watch the last nine weeks
and if you're watching this in the
future go watch the following weeks
until I achieve the 100 to the mill
because I am so make sure you guys hit
that like And subscribe button keeps me
motivated to keep making more videos
like this and I feel like I failed you
guys as a leader and as a mentor this
week by being emotional and breaking my
trading plan and I take that very
serious and I take that to the heart
because my reputation is absolutely
everything and I will not let you guys
down again I will continue to lead by
example and do the correct thing so so
can you guys and have the same results
as me appreciate you guys watching this
video all the way to the end make sure
to hit that like And subscribe button
and set don't forget I'll see you next
week